When $100 million dollars goes missing, the hunter becomes the hunted.
Kill Shot is a action film directed by Ari Novak.
Posing as hunters, a group of terrorists are in search of $100 million that
was stolen and lost in a plane crash en route from Afghanistan.
Jackson Hardison, played by Rib Hillis.
Kate, played by Rachel Cook.
Jim McCluskey, played by Todd Gordon.
Alpha ONE, played by Ari Novak.
Sarah Hardison, played by Xian Mikol.
Dina Diablo, played by Mara Ohara.
Kill is a 2023 Indian Hindi-language action film written and directed by Nikhil
Nagesh Bhat and produced by Dharma Productions and Sikhya Entertainment.
The film, which is inspired by a train robbery experienced by Bhat in 1995, stars Lakshya,
Raghav Juyal, Ashish Vidyarthi, Harsh Chhaya, Tanya Maniktala and Abhishek Chauhan.
Kill premiered at the Toronto International Film Festival on 7 September 2023, where it
was first runner-up for the People's Choice Award: Midnight Madness.
It was also screened at the Tribeca Film Festival in June 2024.
Kill was theatrically released on 5 July 2024 to positive reviews from critics, who praised its cinematrography, visuals,
soundtrack, cast performances and action sequences but criticised the overly graphic violence and plot.
The film grossed ₹47.12 crore against a budget of ₹20 crore.
Kill received fifteen nominations at the 70th Filmfare Awards including  Best Film, Best  Director (Bhat),
Best Male Debut (Lakshya) and Best Supporting Actor (Juyal) and won Best Male Debut (Lakshya).